var questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the tree that is located in Philadelphia's Washington Square Park that was grown from a seed taken on the Apollo 14 mission called?",
        choiceA: "Satellite Seedling ",
        choiceB: "Moon Tree",
        choiceC: "Heaven Tree",
        choiceD: "Space Wood ",
        correct: "Moon Tree",
    },
    {
        question: "When was the Philadelphia Zoo (the oldest zoo in America) chartered?",
        choiceA: "1776",
        choiceB: "1991",
        choiceC: "1859",
        choiceD: "1801",
        correct: "1859",
    },
    {
        question: "How many syllables are in the word Philadelphia?",
        choiceA: "6",
        choiceB: "3",
        choiceC: "2",
        choiceD: "5",
        correct: "5",
    },
    {
        question: "In 1943 the new owner of the Philadelphia Phillies tried to change the name to?",
        choiceA: "Philadelphia Yankees",
        choiceB: "Philadelphia Red Bulls",
        choiceC: "Philadelphia Blue Jays",
        choiceD: "Philadelphia Union",
        correct: "Philadelphia Blue Jays",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the first university in Philadelphia to have both undergraduate and graduate studies?",
        choiceA: "Drexel University",
        choiceB: "University of Pennsylvania",
        choiceC: "Saint Joseph's University",
        choiceD: "Temple University",
        correct: "University of Pennsylvania",
    },
    {
        question: "Philadelphia's motto is Philadelphia maneto. What does it mean?",
        choiceA: "let fraternal respect undergo",
        choiceB: "let understanding apprecation withstand ",
        choiceC: "let sisterly friendship endure",
        choiceD: "let brotherly love endure",
        correct: "let brotherly love endure",
    },
    {
        question: "What was Race Street formerly called?",
        choiceA: "Sassafras Street",
        choiceB: "Main Avenue",
        choiceC: "Church Road",
        choiceD: "Elbow Lane",
        correct: "Sassafras Street",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of the nation's first daily newspaper?",
        choiceA: "The Philadelphia Inquirer",
        choiceB: "The Pennsylvania Packet and Daily Advertiser",
        choiceC: "The Philadelphia Bulletin",
        choiceD: "The Philadelphia Press",
        correct: "The Pennsylvania Packet and Daily Advertiser",
    },
    {
        question: "How many murals are located in Philadelphia?",
        choiceA: "2000+",
        choiceB: "1000+",
        choiceC: "3000+",
        choiceD: "500+",
        correct: "3000+",
    },
    {
        question: "Philadelphia became home to the first general purpose computer in which year?",
        choiceA: "1982",
        choiceB: "1946",
        choiceC: "1991",
        choiceD: "1940",
        correct: "1946",
    },
];